Insert

	db.forms.insert( 
	{ 
		formName: "IPL Survey",
		desc:"IPL players survey",
		type:"form", 
		formData:[{
			questionNo:1,
			question:"Which team you play for?",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Name"
		},
		{
			questionNo:2,
			question:"Where are you from?",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Hometown"
		},
		{
			questionNo:3,
			question:"Role in Team?",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Team"
		}], 
		resCount:4, 
		responses:[
		{
			userName:"Dhoni",
			emailId:"ms@gmail.com",
			answers:[
			{
				questionNo:1,
				question:"Which team you play for?",
				answer:"CSK"
			},
			{
				questionNo:2,
				question:"Where are you from?",
				answer:"Ranchi"
			},
			{
				questionNo:3,
				question:"Role in Team?",
				answer:"Captin, Bastmen, WicketKeeper"
			}]
		},
		{
			"userName" : "Kohli",
			"emailId" : "virat@gmail.com",
			"answers" : [
					{
							"questionNo" : 1,
							"question" : "Which team you play for?",
							"answer" : "RCB"
					},
					{
							"questionNo" : 2,
							"question" : "Where are you from?",
							"answer" : "Delhi"
					},
					{
						questionNo:3,
						question:"Role in Team?",
						answer:"Captin, Bastmen"
					}
			]
        },
		{
			userName:"Jadeja",
			emailId:"jd@gmail.com",
			answers:[
			{
				questionNo:1,
				question:"Which team you play for?",
				answer:"CSK"
			},
			{
				questionNo:2,
				question:"Where are you from?",
				answer:"Gujarat"
			},
			{
				questionNo:3,
				question:"Role in Team?",
				answer:"All-rounder"
			}]
		},
		{
			userName:"Shami",
			emailId:"sham@gmail.com",
			answers:[
			{
				questionNo:1,
				question:"Which team you play for?",
				answer:"DC"
			},
			{
				questionNo:2,
				question:"Where are you from?",
				answer:"Delhi"
			},
			{
				questionNo:3,
				question:"Role in Team?",
				answer:"Pace Bowler"
			}]
		}] 
	})
	
	db.forms.insert( 
	{ 
		formName: "Survey2", 
		type:"form", 
		formData:[{
			questionNo:1,
			question:"Enter Name",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Enter Name"
		},
		{
			questionNo:2,
			question:"Enter emailId",
			inputType:"email",
			placeholder:"Enter Email",
			emailId:"Enter EmailId"
		}], 
		resCount:0, 
		responses:[] } )

Delete

   db.forms.deleteMany( { "type" : "form" } );

Update
	db.forms.update(
	   { formName: "Survey1" },
	   {
		 $push: { responses: 
			 {
                        "userName" : "Kohli",
                        "emailId" : "virat@gmail.com",
                        "answers" : [
                                {
                                        "questionNo" : 1,
                                        "question" : "Which team you play for?",
                                        "answer" : "RCB"
                                },
                                {
                                        "questionNo" : 2,
                                        "question" : "Where are you from?",
                                        "answer" : "Delhi"
                                }
                        ]
                }
		  }
	   }
	)
	
Form
	db.forms.update(
		{ formName: "Survey1" },
		   {
			 $push: { formData: 
				 {
							"questionNo" : "questionNo",
							"inputType" : "inputType",
							"question" : "question",
							"placeholder" : "placeholder",
							"option1":"option1",
							"option2":"option2",
							"option3":"option3"
					}
			  }
		   }
	)

Get

db.forms.aggregate([
                     { $match: { type: "form" } },
                     { $group: { _id: "$formName"} }
                   ])
				   
{(this.state.modal === true)?(<ViewModal toggle={this.toggle} modal={this.state.modal} formDetails={this.state.formData} currentForm={this.state.currentForm}/>):(<ViewModal toggle={this.toggle} modal={this.state.modal} formDetails={this.state.formData} currentForm={this.state.currentForm}/>)}
						  				   
										   
										   
db.forms.insert( 
	{ 
		formName: "Student Registration",
		desc:"Form to capture student details",
		type:"form", 
		formData:[{
			questionNo:1,
			question:"Roll no",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Enter Roll no"
		},
		{
			questionNo:2,
			question:"Standard",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Enter standard"
		},
		{
			questionNo:3,
			question:"Mobile No",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Enter Mobile no"
		},
		{
			questionNo:4,
			question:"Where are you coming from?",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Enter city name"
		}], 
		resCount:3, 
		responses:[
		{
			userName:"Mark",
			emailId:"mk@gmail.com",
			answers:[
			{
				questionNo:1,
				question:"Roll no",
				answer:"0001"
			},
			{
				questionNo:2,
				question:"Standard",
				answer:"Tenth"
			},
			{
				questionNo:3,
				question:"Mobile No",
				answer:"1234567890"
			},
			{
				questionNo:4,
				question:"Where are you coming from?",
				answer:"Royapuram"
			}]
		},
		{
			userName:"Ansari",
			emailId:"ans@gmail.com",
			answers:[
			{
				questionNo:1,
				question:"Roll no",
				answer:"0002"
			},
			{
				questionNo:2,
				question:"Standard",
				answer:"Eleventh"
			},
			{
				questionNo:3,
				question:"Mobile No",
				answer:"0987654321"
			},
			{
				questionNo:4,
				question:"Where are you coming from?",
				answer:"George Town"
			}]
		},
		{
			userName:"Dan",
			emailId:"jd@gmail.com",
			answers:[
			{
				questionNo:1,
				question:"Roll no",
				answer:"0003"
			},
			{
				questionNo:2,
				question:"Standard",
				answer:"Tenth"
			},
			{
				questionNo:3,
				question:"Mobile No",
				answer:"1234567890"
			},
			{
				questionNo:4,
				question:"Where are you coming from?",
				answer:"Adayar"
			}]
		}] 
	})
	
	db.forms.insert( 
	{ 
		formName: "Survey2", 
		type:"form", 
		formData:[{
			questionNo:1,
			question:"Enter Name",
			inputType:"text",
			placeholder:"Enter Name"
		},
		{
			questionNo:2,
			question:"Enter emailId",
			inputType:"email",
			placeholder:"Enter Email",
			emailId:"Enter EmailId"
		}], 
		resCount:0, 
		responses:[] } )